CURRICULUM VITAE

15 September 2021

Vinh Phuc Le Olympiakatu 12 C1 65100 VAASA FINLAND

Mobile: +358 46 540 7847

Email: phuclevinh2000@gmail.com

SCAN HERE TO EXPLORE MY PORTFOLIO



RÉSUMÉ PROFILE

I am currently a senior year IT student at Vaasa University of Applied Sciences, majoring in Information Technology with a specialization in **Embedded System**. During my study at VAMK have remarkably developed my strong work ethic, communication skills, and enthusiasm in algorithm. Besides, I gain the capability of independent working and handling projects with strict time schedules. At university, I have experienced in C++, C programming language, Embedded system design, Linux as well as studies related to the embedded system. I also want to learn and be a full stack developer and learn about many frameworks because we are in technology era, and web development technology is modern and attractive to me. So, I try to learn more about web development with HTML, CSS, React, SASS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, MySQL. I am interested in new digitalization and would love to learn more about them in the manufacturing field. Regarding languages, I acquire native proficiency in Vietnamese and full professional proficiency in English.

WORK EXPERIENCE

May 2021 – Sep 2021 Scandic Hotel (Vaasa)

Part-time housekeeper

- Daily clean the hotel's room.
- Practice the working under a pressure schedule.

Aug 2020 - May 2021 FinnBox Oy (Vaasa)

Part-time newspaper distributor

- Deliver daily newspapers at night shift.
- Practice the working under a pressure schedule.

EDUCATION

Sep 2018 – Now Vaasa University of Applied Sciences, Finland, bachelor's degree

Major: Information Technology, specialized in Embedded system.

SKILLS

React	 Made a Covid Tracker Application Made my portfolio Made Disney Plus clone Made a to-do list application Made a simple Calculator base on Calculator Application from Apple Weather Tracker application Etc.
Bootstrap, Flexbox, SASS, Styled- Components	Familiar with syntaxes and able to apply them
C++ Programming	 Attend to Codeforces programming contests and other coding challenges like Hackerank, Code Abbey, NASA Space App Challenge
C Programming	 Attend to Codeforces programming contests and other coding challenges like Hackerank, Code Abbey, NASA Space App Challenge Create an application offer a possibility to turn a Raspberry Pi as a sound device Create a Modbus system with DHT22 sensor Working with STM32 and sensors using Embedded C
Linux System	 Familiar with the terminal statement as well as Kali Linux. Completed a course related to cyber security at university using Kali Linux.
Microcontroller and Microprocessor	 Familiar with Arduino, Raspberry Pi, STM32 Nucleo Board, RS232, Learn about RTOS.
PCB	 Design and made a PCB circuit of automatic light Design and made a PCB circuit for DHT22 as a slave device and connected with Modbus system
Backend	 Know how to read and fetch data from JSON file. Know how to use Mongoose DB as a database. Know how to GET, PUSH, POST, DELETE using Node.js MySQL
JavaScript	Familiar with syntax, know how to apply to library like React
Languages	Vietnamese Mother tongueEnglish Fluent

More technical projects related to programming at my personal GitHub https://github.com/phuclevinh2000.